Alexey Ivanovskiy

Email: Alexis220382@gmail.com

Skype: alexey.ivanovskiy2 Phone: +375(29)7513014



Personal Statement

Full stack software developer. Mainly I'm working with the most popular Java frameworks such as Spring and Hibernate as well as relational databases. Predisposed to work with both backend and frontend technologies but the web applications is prefer for me.

It is however, my firm belief that the real experience is measured not by the total number of years on the workforce but by projects accomplished, goals achieved and problems solved. I believe that it is more important to have the skills and aptitude to learn quickly and apply various technologies in practice rather than to use the same stack of technologies year after year.

Employment History

EPAM Systems – Minsk, Belarus
Software engineer November 2016 – current

Проект: RPA & AI

Currently, I have led the team in the Customer success direction in the design, configuration and implementation of business processes on one of the RPA (Robotic Processing Automation) and AI (Artificial Intelligent) platform.

To solve the development tasks I use the following technologies: xml, beanshell, groovy, Postgres, MySQL, Amazon Web Services (s3 bucket).

Team framework: Scrum

Freelance – Remote work Java developer August 2016 – November 2016

Project: Survey

As a part-time work, I developed the backend for the site. The site is designed to collect statistics on exciting topics students by creating surveys and making them available to other users of the site. Sheath standard site, includes an authentication system, private office and support.

To solve the development tasks I use the following technologies: Spring IoC, Spring security, Spring MVC, jsp, servlets, MySQL, Amazon Web Services (Elastic compute 2, Elastic beanstalk, Relations database service).

Team framework: Scrum

Sberbank-Technology – Moscow, Russia Software engineer May 2016 – November 2016

Platform: Business development support platform

Project: Data Persist Layer

I am participated in the development of the core platform element. Application module, is being developed by our team daily has to control performance Data Persist Layer in the process of its development and early warning of productivity loss for timely decision-making. In addition, the team is constantly working on technical support and bug fixes of the main project (Data Persist Layer).

To solve the development tasks we use the following technologies: Spring IoC, Spring security, Spring MVC, xml, JAXB, IMDG (In Memory Data Grid), Oracle.

Team framework: Kanban

Sberbank-Technology – Moscow, Russia Software engineer February 2016 – May 2016

Platform: Business development support platform

Project: Registry API

Registry API (one of the main core platform elements). Application module, which was developed by our team, is to maintain a record of all the modules involved in the banking platform. From this module, you can call any process of any module that is registered in the platform. As the interface presented by the module developed by us has the opportunity to make a decision about entering the

registered module into the operation.

To solve the development tasks we use the following technologies: Spring IoC, Spring security, Spring MVC, xml, JAXB, IMDG (In Memory Data Grid), Oracle.

Team framework: Scrum

Freelance projects

Java developer June 2015 – current

It performs a variety of application tasks to freelance exchanges. These were mainly the tasks of performing various laboratory and course work for students of IT specialties. While carrying out this work, I have learned to look at the problem in such a way as they want customers to see it.

Key technologies that I used were in the performance of these tasks: back-end: Spring IoC, Spring MVC, JPA, Hibernate, MySQL, Oracle databases. front-end: Bootstrap, javaFX

Itstart.by – Minsk, Belarus Junior java developer March 2015 – December 2015

It performs a variety of tasks on the school site development on the study of java programming language where I was trained at an early stage.

So, one of the tasks was the development of the test system, which was based on several tests and a separate list of questions. The problem was posed in such a way that any test could include various questions at any stage of testing.

To solve this problem the following technologies were chosen by me such as Spring IoC, JPA, Hibernate, Spring Web MVC and MySQL database.

Armed Forces – Minsk, Belarus Commander anti-aircraft missile division August 2004 – July 2015

I held various management positions from the head of a small unit (3-5 persons) to the commander of a separately located anti-aircraft missile division (70 persons) in the system of air defense troops. In the last post I have had the experience of 5 years. The division, which I was leading, rose from the 9th (last place) till the 1st place in three month and was not below the third place for the whole time that I led it.

The main responsibility was to control combat and economic activity unit.

Personally, I headed the combat crew.

Used mostly not authoritarian, but corporate management style aimed at a minded unity team in combat missions. I tried not to apply any templates for decision-making.

Education

1999-2004 year. Military Academy of the Republic of Belarus. Air defense faculty. "Diploma engineer of radio."